all
right here it is it's the what is it
22nd
yeah we are outside
um we're outside of Spirited
cyclist I'm going to start using this is
my starting off point
um for all my bike streams um because
it's a it's a local bike shop i r in
really great really great group of
people here uh I don't remember all
their names but I've always had a really
great experience with them I try to give
them as much money as I
can
um about my specializ shoes here I'm
actually thinking about um approaching
them about posting some of my
rides um um sort of community rides to
the bulletin board
somewhere particularly the one I'm going
to do this Friday coming up where we're
going to ride to Charlotte for critical
mass and I'm towing I was towing with
the idea of starting up another monthly
starting out at monthly uh group ride uh
on the goblin route and take as many
people as they want to go on the goblin
route or on shorter versions of the
goblin
route so it's a really great really
great little shop up
here um they close on uh right now but I
think they close on Monday as well how
you doing
Jesus
so hey kasham how are
you oh his head on
nice that's fantastic so one of the
reasons I came here is I want to try a
very Community friendly bike
route um that is
is you
know extremely Community
friendly so we're going to go down some
some I want to I want to ask myself
during this entire
ride if somebody was fit enough to do
it would they be able to do this safely
and I think the answer is yes I like to
go on safe safe
routes I'm more about the joy of cycling
than I am about high performance I do
like a good fast ride
but particularly today we're going to be
doing really slow
ride um and this these videos are being
posted to YouTube now I have created a
playlist called daily cycling
blog so if somebody wants something
interesting
to watch while they are doing their
indoor ride or whatever it might
be we are going to stop for most of the
stop
signs not all but
most we're actually going to pass the
storage
unit
so this is another reason I like this
particular
ride this is this new storage unit that
I
got right here with my my all my bike
stuff is
here little bike shop there we will be
doing some videos about bike maintenance
and stuff like that just like tons and
tons of
videos about that stuff so I don't need
to do it but
people have questions and they're just
learning they could ask could do that I
actually need to go into the mini
storage
and finish moving a bunch of stuff over
there I'm trying something new with
audio yesterday I had the stereo
backwards so if you have headphones on
you should get a little bit of an ASMR
audio thing going on today
so here's talking to the left ear here's
talking to the right
ear I told you today is going to be a
very easy day could be upwards of 3
hours based on how slow I'm going to go
we have really high
heat we're like 85 or 90 degrees right
now
and I pushed pretty hard yesterday I did
a Tempo ride
yesterday
so today's ride's going to
be mostly me sit sitting down just
enjoying it nice happy Sunday
ride have a number of we can take when
we get
here and I actually think I want to
try a trail option that we haven't done
before
most of my bike rides are focused
on the
scenery scenery and
safety those are the things I
like hey look we're on an official bike
path what do you
know it's so happens the official back
path goes straight
here
and he not particularly good we'll do it
one
day a little bit of a better one over
here and we are going
to cross
here this is the only dangerous road and
probably it's pretty light traffic so
there's a share
this is Davidson so it's pretty tame
especially on a
Sunday when we come back we'll go
through down downtown
Davidson believe it or not downtown
Davidson is usually pretty dead on
Sunday let take a left
tier hook up
with a
Greenway it's going to head into
Pine exclamation point route will show
you the regular Goblin
route we're just modifying that a little
bit sounds like I got a
loose
spoke yeah I know what's going on
something's making noise down
there one the reasons I I love rvel
biking Adventure biking is because the
bike
is more
quiet I don't like noising anything
hey
Ted do your thing come on what are you
doing what are we doing
[Music]
I am a little frustrated Americans do
not they see a bike and they freeze they
don't know what to do do I stop do I let
him pass me what do I
do answer the same thing with any other
vehicle I see dead
people now we're going to be climbing
this hill at the
end
so let me know
I yeah I do stop for stop
signs but particularly in Suburban
areas if it's
safe the the most annoying stop sign
thing drama that I have is not when
people run stop signs which is obviously
bad but
when when they tell you to go
particularly if there's a another person
at the stop sign because the other
person is thinking okay I'm going to
treat him like a
car and the other one is like waving me
on and the car is like the other car is
like I don't know what's going on here
and so they go thinking they're waiting
for them and that's a
problem that my friends is a is a
problem all right we're going to go on
the trail here there's two two ways to
get on the trail I was going to take you
on the more picturesque route you know
what we could do that let's do that we
could go under the bridge twice this is
a really really elegant Bridge it's
really beautiful so we'll go under it
twice there's a really nice Wood Bridge
here old school Wood
Bridge modeled after the the kind you'd
find all over the south in this area
East Antiquity
Bridge we're not going to go through the
bridge there it is isn't that beautiful
I should probably take a picture right
there
we'll go in the green
way you know we can almost
do we can almost do the route backwards
no
wonder should we do the route
backwards we
could I'm feeling the desire to do the
route
backwards holy
cow you know now with the
tunnel I realize we can do the route
backwards
yeah why not you
know keep it
fresh it used to be with the with the
crossing the
highway yeah one way crossing the
highway used to
be really dangerous because it
was you know know kind of an
uphill going the backwards way it was
uphill so you were even slower acrossing
the highway and the cars really hate
that and so you know you go the other
way and you know you keep your speed up
and you fly down the
highway and know cars don't
complain but now that we have the tunnel
we found the tunnel which we found about
a month ago two months ago it goes under
the
highway there's really no reason like
literally no reason not to go backwards
this is great
information because I can switch it up
every
day
mhm another thing that's nice about that
is it'll keep that'll keep the content
kind of fresh it's already fresh
because every day there's a little bit
of
a change in the
surroundings weekends are nice and
quiet weekdays are
you know school kids then you have the
seasonal changes so there's there's the
same route is pretty interesting but
being able to reverse the route that's
going to make it even more
interesting like that pond we just
passed normally I'm flying down this
road we never get a chance to really see
it super happy about
that little bit of a climb coming for
sure here now as I said usually I'm
flying downhill here
this going to put our ride about three
hours bunny
bunny I should shut up I'll shut up
now look at this bridge is this
one it's a hot one huh it is a hot one
it's a good question let me get my
breath cat Catch My Breath
here that is a great great
little Bridge they made for us
that a little bit I was like
normally this is our climb uphill I
should have took more advantage of that
downhill
okay because they going straight up zed
that thing is like 4% and I'm
tired let give me a
break I'm only I'm going 10 m an hour
what is that 14 km an hour 15 16 I don't
know boy I haven't been in this
intersection going this direction in a
long time
it probably won't even see
me this is
fun beautiful day Amen
brother oh hey look at
that up to the left is the next to the
Walgreens is where the comic book store
is
normally I'm flying behind cars going
the other direction
here is the angle of the camera okay
everybody I like it so it looks like
you're riding a bike
they painted over the the bike lane that
used to be here or they got rid of
it they put cheros
instead East Coast what's
up East Coast
represent what are the hell are they
doing
here like some sort of cult thing
what is that about they're like ready
break
I might actually end up preferring this
direction because it means I get to go
through the CRP M little
faster I'm allergic
you catch the slide just right that'll
be nice
y don't you
turn only left Channel I turned them
both on
I asked about that
earlier guess I could fix it right
now let me
look I can't really see
it no it has left and right check one
too
check one
two it says left and
right the Right comes and
goes okay that one's
right this is left is it
because connection issue I think it
might just be because I'm talking into
the right one
more that might
be that's not
centered right right right left left
left I'll wait around for you to confirm
that before I go actually let me cross
all
screen it could be the mic it could be
the mics have a
problem it's back I mean it was there
before so I don't know maybe maybe maybe
it was just because of my I wasn't
positioned right over the top
[Music]
I I don't
know it might be the mic is is broken
though that also could be so yeah keep
keep me informed on that I'll I'll make
sure to go check the
thing it's not
Bluetooth
no it I don't know what the techn is
it's the it's the receiver on
the it's the receiver that comes with
the it's built into the DJI
camera I I think what you're probably
experiencing is like me talking over the
right side like this I think I think the
mics were not centered underneath
me as it is right now the right mic is
like a
millimeter
closer so
I'm sorry a centimeter closer and so the
right side's probably always going to
get picked up before the
left I am working to fix
that I tried a new new mic position
today okay this
sucks so this this is
definitely this Crossing that we're
doing right
here this is way way worse
this Crossing is way
worse
yeah that's good to know the coming the
other way is pretty easy but this is
this has got all kinds of problems cuz
I'm going to have to get in the turn
lane
here yeah this is not going to
happen I'm going to have to just walk it
onto the
sidewalk
yeah nor I can ride with traffic there
but not not if I'm going to do
[Music]
that yeah we have to rethink that I'm
sure I can do that
better rental app was a good start
by CC clock I don't even know what that
is
so this is going to be a really fast
descent though
youj
2.4 yeah but it's like the I wish I had
a table I could
use because there the mics are literally
3 in from the
camera I mean I I powered them up full
power
so there is maybe one of
them that is not working as well cuz it
it did get wet once upon a time I don't
remember which
one cloth rental app clothing
rental I don't know maybe
this is this is not a very good downhill
I don't like it at all it's got so many
bumps on it this is really bad bad Road
all right so this is good to know I
never realized how bad this road was
because I was always climbing
it but going down it sucks I'm
definitely not keeping this road on the
route for this
direction that there's a especially when
there's a total like bike path a paved
bike path you know what
you guys we got time there's no rush
today so I'm actually going to
go the pathway that I want to do
that's a bit smoother than this and give
it a
try and a back track yes you don't why
I'm going up I don't even like this road
at all to tell you the truth I I don't
I've talked about it last
night it's got CRP mytle on it they
don't maintain it
it doesn't have any shoulders so when
people occasionally swing by but not
much it's not very it's not very
visually
interesting the bike route um path is
not a lot more interesting to watch than
this are we offline
completely what the hell is going on
here we're still here right
I don't know what's going on with my
box it says it's pushing 10,000 kilit so
must be
okay I don't know what that that
business even would look like you want
to rent clothes to
people I mean I imagine there's a demand
for it
hope you can hear me
bug on
me stop
sign there's lots of car so I'm going to
stop okay so this is the
road this road has been bad in the past
but last year they repaved it and they
put a bike lane on
it like you need to get get an interview
or
something you find a hole in your pants
Target
people I
mean
wow I mean I I don't know how you would
make it profitable
honestly
um I I don't I don't
know there's the transit the
I I mean I'm not trying to I just
can't I there's no way I would have ever
used any kind of service like that and I
came from really poor family with eight
children I was the oldest I had to work
from the time I was 11 actually
10 it was 11 or 12 12 12 I a paper
boy and if I wanted anything I had to
buy
it and but there was never a job
interview that I would have done that I
didn't
have sufficient clothes
for using your example I
don't I mean there are services like
that right it's particularly for women
and I'm sorry to be gender specific but
there's already Services well the rent
close for a prom
or you know they even have more casual
people that are really into
fashion maybe if it was a
high-end fashion clo rental
service but you'd have to have
ridiculously high Insurance cuz people
would ruin the clothes they'd rent the
clothes to go
party or to do something and they end up
ruining him it's really easy to
do
and I would guess the people that would
be attracted to renting
clothing would be the same kind of
people who like to party
guard because they want to look nice
they want to go to a
club I mean why does anybody dress up
these days right to get pictures taken
to go to the prom and to
party cuz they want to get some you
know and
I just I feel like that would
be really hard to keep the stuff that
you rent from getting destroyed on the
first
rental you
know I mean yeah I feel I feel like the
business model that would be really
hard could be
wrong yeah where on I I know people who
do
that I I know someone specifically in
mind right now who does that very
thing he's really into
fashion he does worse things he'll he'll
order stff from Amazon and say he never
got
it which I think is Despicable
but for some reason he thinks it's okay
to do that
I just I don't think it would be
viable first of all if it's America and
you're trying to do it
yourself I'm I'm going to strongly as
strongly as I
can suggest that you do not start a
business in
America unless you're getting Silicon
Valley venture capital
the idea that you can start your own
business and survive in America is a
myth I know that from firsthand
experience there's no money there's no
Venture Capital you'll end up with no
Ira no retirement because you'll use
your own money you have no protections
because you can't Ur bankruptcy if you
financed it yourself when you can
but you just can't do it it's actually
one of the things not to get political
but it's one of the things toml Harris
talks about given the 50 ,000 startup
business thing to to help the middle
class have
jobs one of the one of the this one of
the
downsides of
losing being late stage capitalism the
way we are in America is there is no
middle class and as that gets worse and
worse that means everybody is doing
something for somebody else they'll have
either a service job or they're sitting
back fat cat making money just for doing
nothing because of all their Investments
or something because they control the
money and as capitalism gets worse and
worse and worse which it is that FR
fractures it even more which makes it
even harder for people in the middle
class not to mention the
monopolies the people in the power they
have such powerful monopolies if they if
they want to get into the business they
flip a button you know or they they snap
their fingers and they they put you out
of
business you
know and it used to be the Silicon
Valley people would at least compete to
be bought
out they would get bought out and
then you know
and then they'd be ultra Ultra Rich
Millionaires and then they'd stay for a
year and bail which is why I hate
Silicon
Valley pursuing other interests
really that actually happened I'm
speaking of big fix with IBM then IBM
got rid of it later when they realized
how big a it was but the guys who
made it and con IBM into buying it out
became old multimillionaires
for conning IBM into buying it that's a
true story
they don't see it that way that's
exactly what they did
though hey should we
stay on the trail today let's do
that oh yeah if you're running your own
show yeah I ran my own business
myself I paid Tas and and refunds on
their
own stuff and my wife helped me with
taxes that was
it I'm still paying for that
still paying for it because all it takes
is one unexpected turn of events like
your landlord taking your rent away
taking your place of business away and
saying I don't no sorry I want this back
boom no
business all it takes is something like
that and you're you're
destitute and you're facing $50 $60,000
wor the debt like I still am my point is
don't go into business for yourself in
America just say no to that it's a total
lie
don't do it keep a big
job suckle from the tee of corporate
America particularly in
Tech
right and then do a side hustle do a
side hustle and make money on the side
doing the thing that you want to do and
then make that side hustle
profitable and then and only then either
after you got it bought out or you can
do it full- time give up now to be fair
that's what I did did with skill stack
for a year and a half I ran it by myself
while I was also working at
IBM but it turned out to be too much so
I took $60,000 of my retirement money
out gave myself a year to to build it
and I did I built it successfully it was
actually very profitable too profitable
so profitable I ended up doing things
based on the income that I shouldn't
have I should have been more
conservative because I knew the money
was coming and then all of a sudden my
landlord pulled a rug out and I was
stuck with a bill
I don't like talking about that makes me
very
angry there was no reason by the way for
the landlord pulled the bill I had paid
my rent on time every time and this
Shady
made me deposit cash into a
specific well spargle account at a
specific bank that I had to ride my bike
to every single month
and I had to I had to tell him what the
account for I had to I had to write the
check out to to his wife's like side
hustle business it was totally
shady the guy was totally illegal he
didn't want to pay taxes on
it so he was filtering all this rent
money through this tax
shelter should I should have turned him
in when he pulled the plug at me because
I told them that the ripping nails were
causing people to be concerned for their
safety because they he roofed my they
took tore all the roof off of our place
without telling us anything came in one
day to work and all these grandmas and
kids are walking around roofing nail
rusted roofing nails sticking up in my
entryway I got mad about it and I said
dude you didn't tell us about that he
like well we had to do it I'm
like I have grandma's and their camp kid
dropping their Camp kids off walking
around your roofing nails because of you
he got pissed off pulled the plug out
told me I had to be out in the a month I
had no
recourse nothing I could
do destroyed my business IM immediately
we had an agreement that he was going to
let us stay there for 5 years which I
didn't put on paper I should have he
came through because we were about to
remodel and
reinvest I about $225,000 worth of M
computers to reinvest in the place
within two months I was being kicked
out I'm telling you do not start a
business in America there's too much
risk unless you have somebody else
bearing the financial burden of the risk
like some fat cat venture
capitalist don't do it just say
no corporate job with a hobby
yeah I think that's what you should do
all these people that want to become
game devs I'm like are you sure have you
seen what they do to game
developers they destroy them they
destroy game developers
lives it's like talk about a sweat
shop like you really
don't you think you
do what you really want to do is work
for a corpor
job and then spend all your free
time making that really cool app that
you want to make that's what you really
want to
do same thing with people who like
become professional artists or musicians
it's very very rare for them to remain
doing that and be able to pay for it and
still enjoy
it that's
actually that's actually the primary
theme of one of my favorite movies of
all time a Woody Allen movie Woody all's
kind of a prick but I don't
care um Matthew MCC not Matthew MCC um
Owen
Wilson in uh Midnight in
Paris and he's a Hollywood hack he's
making really really great
money from it's one of the best movies
ever it's so good if you haven't seen
Midnight in Paris you should go watch
that
with somebody you truly love don't watch
it with your wife that you're having a
problem with
because it has a problematic wife in it
who's just like my ex-wife by the
way if she's the daughter she's just
like entitled rich girl and they go to
they go to Paris and she her mommy Rich
Mommy and Daddy are there and Owen's
just writer and in his heart he's always
wanted to be a writer just a pure writer
write a novel maybe and he's sold out
because he's a really good writer so he
writes for
Hollywood and he makes lots and lots of
money
and there's actually a scene where
they're all sitting at the dinner table
and like I've seen what he makes but
still he worries me with this novel
talk and you know this Republican
father-in-law is like judging him oh
squirrel it's like judging him based on
more
squirrels squirrels on
Parade he's judging it based on how much
money he
makes tra is great isn't
it it's good from this
direction so anyway his dream is become
a writer right so he spends his time in
Paris and something magical happens at
midnight where he's roaming the streets
of Paris and he asked his wife he's like
you want to go roam the streets of Paris
with me romantically in the middle of
the night she's like no I'm going to go
to bed and he does and something really
amazing
happens it's really magical it's amazing
it's I'm going to go watch it tonight
the show oh who what is
this is there a squirrel what is that
like six
squirrels there's another one trying to
get a
nut three worst movies oh I don't know I
I don't I watched a little bit of the
Stevens theall movie the other day and I
was like oh my God can't say I ever
watched the whole thing
Midnight in Paris is a really good movie
if you want to be
inspired because it it helps you realize
that it's okay to chase your dreams
and
stuff but there's this there's a
line he keeps having these these things
happen to him at
midnight
and he tries to tell his wife about him
but she doesn't want to hear about it
she doesn't
care and at one point she goes goes well
I don't know maybe I'd have some time to
work on my novel God there must have
been 20 squirrels we just passed there
got to be at least 20
squirrels there's another
one best spider ever
see a g doesn't even know how
to
fight he'd get his hand ass handed to
him at any stage of his career he was
always a fake
anyway
so so they
um his ex-wife I mean his wife is like
actually his fiance it's not his wife
yet that's the thing he's all worried
about marrying ANZ because she's got all
this she's kind of you know got baggage
she's I'm so glad he ends up not
marrying her spoiler
alert and
he tells
her well know maybe I could work on my
novel if we get some time we could move
here they got all the money in the world
they don't need money is not their
concern and she says to
him do you really want to
struggle and that line my wife and I
love this movie so that line has become
kind of a kind of a mantra meme
line that we say all the time to each
other do you really want to struggle
every time something that we want to do
becomes
hard we just kind of use that line
ironically it's like but yeah Rob do you
really want to struggle
Rob
because she's
like trying Chuck Norris had actual
skills he did don't believe me watch him
go go at it with Brule
Stephen seal lies about knowing Bruce
Lee are we going to have this
argument he strong biceps with you're
talking about his 350 lb blob of a the
dude's disgusting the go has always been
disgusting no form no
technique nothing just a bunch of
ego
yeah could he still kick my ass probably
I'm a wimpy yoga guy riding a bike with
no
neck for other reasons not because I'm
morly obese three times
over I always love these like badasses
who grow up and let themselves become
whales for no reason just cuz they're
undisciplined lazy with
the uigos
like the Buddhists say hey look we're at
burkdale
already usually we're at Birkdale at the
end of the
ride h i could just turn around and go
back why
not free
scooter how the speaker is St
working mics I
mean kind of could get I kind of want to
ice
cream should we get an ice
cream get ice cream
I really shouldn't but I want one so
there my look like a huge
one are you guys in line or oh we're
still picking you go ahead we're oh
okay hi welcome hi which is
the is okay and you want um let me make
sure I get my
wallet is this your first time here um
second but it's been a while so just for
remind oh crunchy hazelnut all the way
oh my God please we also have the um
chocolate hazelnut cookies and cream oh
that looks good
too all right now okay we got to wait
our I don't know about that that's hard
that one just looks so good let's try
we'll try I guess I'll do that one too
crunchy looks good let's try the crunchy
one which base would you like we could
do a vanilla a Belgian chocolate maybe
that would um
coconut coconut oh wait that's
vegan I mean that's fine I guess yeah
okay let's
that
any would you like it full dip or just
half I don't know what that means so we
can do it half dip like the picture with
the dark chocolate or or we can do like
both sides with the cat on it I mean is
the cost the same yeah same yeah do the
whole thing go for it why would you
not I don't I'm trying to figure that
out I guess maybe there's some reason so
the full dip is way better but the half
dip just looks prettier it looks pretty
yeah well I can I can see that okay
anything else for you nope that is
[Music]
all did you want to join our Awards
program um what the hell why
not can you give me something to fill
out later cuz I can't actually let's do
that they got a big crowd here let me
let me uh can I do that online excuse me
can I do that online because I come
through here all the time I do this
pretty much every day
so I'll do that I'll do that next time
okay you can always also do it just um
okay okay yeah it plus it's slower on
the weekend I I mean on
weekday you guys
[Music]
all
right that's great I'm just going to um
carry it actually I can
get yeah I thank you so much you're
welcome
want to drop
that let's see we can find some place to
[Music]
sit what the hell is this
am I going to get
[Music]
demonetized how long did this ride last
we're not even like a third of the ride
in and I'm already buying food must be
Sunday Sunday funay
[Music]
yeah look at I demonetize me on YouTube
I don't care you can't I'm sitting right
under a
speaker
yeah 49 minutes and 38 seconds so that's
like literally half halfway in about
it's about we we're on about two and a
half hours 3
hours I try to see if I can see my
ice cream look at this pretty ice
cream like that's all the calories for
the day right
[Music]
there wa tell we go people
watch I could kind of walk around
gosh brain
freeze wa he's standing
[Music]
up I
know let's like scope it out
let's see what else there is we're
walking around no one's going to steal
my bike it's got my alarm on
[Music]
it I just want to drink of
water I want I
a like a baby cold but
[Music]
what is this
about I don't know what that
about I don't it's about
anything we used to work
there I don't see her
anymore like a it like um
some kind of cookie place now it's
really good thank
you I'm making a whole noise with my
shoes I feel like that guy that
guy that was good
[Music]
kind of a big
popsicle hell no
why would I
silly I don't care about back anywhere
really my wife laughs at me because she
in New
York I'm very
foolishly trusting
[Music]
am i r
no oh yeah tons of
eies
mhm I think my camera's got face
tracking
on
yeah that was the Cyber truck parked
Chara yesterday
yday this exact
spot hey snip skunk snip sunk Mak wants
to call you
skunk I don't know
man good question
this just made me wicked
thirsty is that
Friday let's go look at me
word I should have clip that those rich
girls with a golf cart I said you'd have
to be a to own one of those and
they're like park next to the Cyber
truck
I don't think they appreciated
[Music]
that drop a truth bomb on
them people put their fingers in the
Trunks and slam it and critically injure
their fingers just to prove that they're
awesome oh paddle
boarding guys I was obsessed with paddle
boing I started the paddle board meet up
in
Charlotte yeah I'm not even
lying in 2013 I started the Charlotte
CLT paddle board
up I haven't done anything with it since
then I still own the domain
[Music]
name that's a shitty
power totally shap
power it's okay doesn't have to be the
best no sh powerboard is better than no
power until it sinks it's inflatable I'm
pretty sure no it's not it's not RoR
modal
either is this bahana I actually met all
the people who make all the owners of
the paddle board I went to outdoor
retailer in 2013 or
14 they sent me he paid for me to go
gave me the ticket and
this fun I got to meet a bunch of like
the world champion paddle Bo what's his
name back then I got to paddle with him
actually for a while it was really cool
he took me out for a private for
Obsession really cool cuz I told him I
started P meet up in heill was like
promoting the the the sport and
everything and he was like oh that's
awesome he kind we kind of broke off
from the pack it was really cool I I
felt like a rock I have a picture
somewhere of it me and him I was like
this pudgy old guy in my 40s he's this
like super hot
Hawaiian who just won like he just won
the the he just won the stand up
competition in Hawaii on
[Music]
Malachi
anyway wish J was better
that's a tough one depends on what you
are
judging you're talking about
money oh my God there's a ramp I've been
looking for the ramp where there it
[Music]
is wow
and really again really nice CH check I
think that was
tremble to get a nice little chip on
Crosby and and I
back well I'll beate
you all right
which company would I go back if they
help me another
job um neither of them
actually I would I wouldn't go back to
work for a company I work for a pretty
good company
now I might go to work for
myself and get a get a Consulting gig or
[Music]
something now normally they go right
here on our way back home but now we're
going the opposite way
so car behind me is getting annoyed I
don't give a
I'm going I'm going it's
red uh-oh
I'm a bad boy
I probably would have started to stop
and hit the brakes and end up stopping
in the middle of the intersection
absolutely gorgeous time of
year a little bit of Summer hanging
on probably the ideal
temperatures still
summerish great time to be outside
I mean it should
be
24 I think it should be
working I forgot to pair it with my
Garmin
though bad me I got to do
that
Tony two Z and
KN why does that make me think of Pros
the
plakes I'm sure you get that all the
time5 I'm just telling you what my I
don't make these numbers
up 75 in Philly
wow wait did I go too
far should I go too
far oh my God it's so beautiful
here hey we're on a
this is one of those days where I end up
like staying on the bike for like 4
hours cuz it's just so
fun I got to figure out a way
to keep my batteries my mic batteries
charged and going get a little tiny
battery
pack
faight I know guys I apologize but I
switched everything back
I know I I got a massive up Cry of
anger I would really like to know if the
percentage of people watching me are
from you know more of them are
Fahrenheit people versus
Celsius but I uh I was I was uh metric
system for a long time mostly because it
whipped and then I haven't been doing
whipped lately so it's not a big of deal
anymore I switched back from my trip I
could be convinced to
uhoh that gray is not good we got to
check out what's causing
that why are we getting
gray yeah starlink is
failing cuz there's so many
trees
yeah it's coming back though
I do both I don't know about
that I mean I
could I guess I could put it on the
opposite
side I know I mean it's only so I I
already feel bad giving up the screen
real estate to that stuff because a lot
of people on YouTube finding my video
they're not going to want to see my
numbers right I mean maybe they will
turn congestive hours like right now
yeah it's St actually really going to be
worth it when we get to the
Greenways where there's not good there's
not good cell sell
reception this little this little ride
right here is a lot more fun this this
part right
here you're a stats
person you know it's
better I mean I've seen people I would
love to put Power on my screen too I
think that would be
fun pel Tom has that I I did it I got it
working the way pel Tom had
it
but I it's kind of overbearing
and detracts from the immersion and
stuff 3 ft = 1
M
yeah I actually like kly Rams and I I
love the the metric system for height
I'm exactly 174
CM when I tell somebody my height in
inches it's like 5'8 and a half I don't
like saying
that St sign kind have a blind one I
don't know what I'm getting here so oh
it's a CEST back okay good to
know I mean if I put conversion numbers
on there it might be good for the
universe right what's too bad is you
can't combine the numbers into a single
query those are all independent queries
so they have independent little bounding
boxes and they got to be pasted together
in weird
ways I I think you can get around that
but
I there is somebody who made kind of a
thing for that
but I don't
know
maybe you know what I should do is uh
I should make a command how about
that what if I made a
command that's what I should
do I should have a command called
stats and the first argument should
be
metric
right we should have a just so if
somebody wanted to
see cuz some people can't see the screen
you know it's kind of small on their
screens cuz they're on a phone or
something you know especially if they're
watching chat and the video on their
phone some people do that I do that I do
that in bed all the time while I'm
dozing off to
sleep I'll pull up a twitch stream and
just kind of watch it while I fall
asleep oh hey look blinky light cyclist
my light is not on because these roads
are not dangerous I don't need it
hey hi it's also the reason I don't wear
a
helmet
suei so far this reverse trip has been
very
pleasant it's been very pleasant indeed
I kind of like the idea of fueling up
for the rest of the ride at
birdale how much that thing cost me I
didn't even ask I just bought it was it
like five bucks could buy buy like a
gallon of ice
cream the same
amount I thought about um I mean cuz I
got an adventure bike right October 12th
there's Ride with GPS has an
event it's
called uh outdoor coffee and they have
these meetups where you everybody rides
bikes there and then makes coffee
outside and have a big Meetup people
that like to ride their bikes just for
the pleasure of it who have Gear to to
take a coffee maker with
them well I was thinking about doing
that
right I'm going to start bringing my
coffee maker and
my outdoor meal
stuff we go some place fun
and Mountain's got snow
really I believe it
Colorado Mountains for
sure that's how you know Colorado in
places like that are getting cold cuz
it's getting nice and good
here you know did I turn
early a
idea or is
it did I turn
early I think I did
yeah I'm too
early I
think where am I going what's my
name do horse ride with me
never we're we're very seriously once we
get settled in November we're going to
buy a cargo
trike and she's totally down she almost
bought it we were talking about it and
she was so excited she almost paid the
money and bought it right there or like
bucks we're going to buy a Schwin cargo
trike it's got a big old basket on it
big old area for like groceries and
stuff it's a three-wheel bike
tricycle did I just say three- wheel
bike oh my
God sometimes I try to help people out
because I don't know if they know
English and I do the wrong thing and I
say stuff like that
doesn't make any
sense oh God she she'll go shopping the
problem with that is we pretty much
decided to buy a fresh produce from
Harris teer because it's by our house
and ALDI doesn't always have the best
stuff and we can also order stuff from
Amazon and stuff so she's down with
paying a little bit
more
and doing
that that is
beautiful so she's going to ride the
trike
so those things don't go very fast at
all I thought about riding the
trike I thought about this is one of the
things we're
considering parking the trike at the
house and having it be their
taxi so anybody needs to go anywhere
they need jump on
it I know it is
ugly and we're doing my Goblin route
reverse to mix it
up so this I used
to
so oh the neighborhood the neighborhoods
on this route are absolutely Exquisite
that's why I love it so much this this
bike
route
anyway
so so yeah my wife's got a
trike she's going to get a trike and
then but I thought about taking the
trike
to wait
what oh that's
interesting this cuts
through I had no
idea I had no idea see we could eat
there we could like have a little picnic
when it when the fall Hits we're going
to start doing
that I might actually instead of going
gang busters for 3 hours i' go I'm
thought about going for 90 minutes and
taking a break cuz I got all the stuff
right and I could just make make coffee
or make a meal or get it you know
smoothie out of my
thermos instead of paying like
$9 and then I can still have a
break we can do it someplace
interesting okay this hill is not fun
this hill is usually fun the other way
it's called downhill
so far I'm loving this
direction I
know October
12th out coffee
outside ugly I think there's actually a
Meetup right by
you they're going to have an outdoor
meet up where cyclists just all meet and
have coffee outside
if you go to Ride with
GPS they have an event they're putting
on they want to sell you stuff that's
why they they part they they want to
sell you like a Raa drip coffee
maker oh there's this swim
housee from the other
direction yeah
I see I could have gone left there
actually it would have been better I
wouldn't lost
momentum pickle
ball where have all the pickle Ballers
gone was it that trendy was it as trendy
as Pokémon
bike cruising L 20 M
hour uphill
he's pedaling I'll give him
that meanwhile the old
[Laughter]
guy I got nothing against
ebikes it just saps my soul when they go
flying past
me like
really back in my day we had to Pedal
our
bikes you young whippers
snappers with your ebikes and your e
bones and your your e
bat where am
I where am
I I have no idea where I
am I really don't I'm not even
kidding I think this is
it I could be wrong though I do not know
where I
am help
me I'm on Chadley
apparently if they want turn hey hi
beautiful spiders they have
there yeah we going to get all the
October stuff coming out all the
Halloween All Hallows
Eve takes the edge off of being
completely
lost an America
dumbass you smart ass so many smart
asses
Hugh Torrance that's not a good sign
this is not a fun road to be on No in
fact yeah there's my turn off I know
where to go now if I take this all the
way out the other side I'll end up on
this like
Strode that's a word I was reminded by
pixel pixel reminded me of the strods
and tanked my dream of Salt Lake and
briam young univers Brigham Young
inventing the grid system of strods
I was like damn he actually wasn't
enlightened at all he made the worst
thing possible for urban traffic
management Lost In
Paradise Suburban Paradise this I hope
this isn't a dead
end yo what's up what's up what's up
does this go
through like I don't know leave us alone
dude okay yeah I guess it
does stranger danger stranger I am the I
am king of
cringe I am the guy with no front
teeth that you should fear on all Halls
Eve I should dress up for the Halloween
bike I'm going to bike but I'm going to
dress
up yeah what should my costume
be I want to make it so that when I do
my regular daily
commute which is a big loop cuz I work
at home I want to make it so
that I have some character so I had a
wizard hat last
year it's great oh hell yeah I mean
usually it's fun when you do with a
group but because everybody knows me on
this
route you know I'm on the same route
every day same
time it would be really fun to
like ham it up also I'm so old people
don't give a ugly knows this that's
why I like ugly so much she also doesn't
give a
oh
look I'll never forget that man I will
I'm sorry I've never going to there's so
many examples but that's still one of my
favorite like this big snot thing falls
on her leg and she's like oh well I got
snot on my leg okay then she just keeps
on busting ass I don't know she's like
digging Trails
or I don't
know like smashing the bombing the
trails that she just
made
meanwhile Rob does the same
Suburban road every
day I can push my limits I'm going to
put let's think about this what costume
should I wear you were be Wings last
Aller in your road oh my God that sounds
so cute God you're probably is so
adorable yeah did you did you have all
the spandex cyclist chasing
you there's a be over there I'm going to
go get that
be you be like
n
n at least at least ugly's been around
enough for us to make inappropriate
comments about beautiful women on my
ride one of which I actually said hey
ugly and she looked and she thought I
was talking about her that there's a
clip of that that's like one of my
favorite moments of all time on switch
hey oh my God is this killer Hill oh my
God we so bombing this thing this is the
hill I'm always sucking sucking wind now
I can scream down it I can scream down
it yes
oh
baby 5 50 Watts
baby all right
inevitable law of gravity and
elevation if you go down you must come
up you've got reverse goo more often yes
that's what I'm trying to say I can like
switch it up now
right also I don't care about speed and
training and so just getting out
there remembering I'm a human being or a
human bee
I could dress like a bee cuz all my
colors are so flashy it would double his
visibility oh my God wait this used to
be a fun Hill to go
down oh my
God oh my
God okay I'm going to go over
here I'm
tired that's also a fun Hill look at
him everything's so
dead all right going
tennis they're playing actual tennis not
picky ball pickle
ball actual
tennis what the
hell Haven got the Mo tennis isn't cool
it's hoing pickall
now they're literally ripping out tennis
courts right now we will pass one to put
more pickle ball
in now this is really
unfortunate here's a big old downhill I
can't even
use or can I if I wait till the exact
possible moment
like right now okay go
baby oh now I have to slow down
because
bumps bu hop that
nope too
heavy I know oh I got my adventure bike
and got
my super
awesome I may have crashed there once on
my carbon
bike am I acting I am aren't
I I feel I feel
seen
God also ice
cream were you here for the ice
cream this is a good idea I need to
start getting ice cream in the first
half of the
ride
mhm and it can like fill me full of
sugar high and
endorphins oh
boy we're doing the reverse so burkdale
is at the beginning so I got an ice
cream like a quarter of the way
in
bigot you can't see big foot when I'm
going the other way cuz I'm going too
fast yet another reason
sugar oh I know it does it really
changes especially simple
sugars hey
yeah come
coming it smells like literally
because there's this bike trail is made
on a sewer
path if you go to sleep
dead I will sing you a nighttime l
lby or
not just listen to The
Crickets in the crazy rantings of an old
man that'll put you to
sleep puts my wife to sleep
I was talking to her while she was
dozing off while I was folding my
laundry see his
head what I say about
sewers right
oh my God it stink so
bad I still need to squirt
my right cleat it's very
noisy going to be the tunnel pretty soon
is it me or does this feel like it's
going faster than the other time in the
other
direction maybe because it's all
new to me it's not but you know what I
mean what the hell stop
squeaking and good afternoon to you too
sir
bird ugly hasn't seen this
part have you seen the tunnel that goes
under the highway ugly this is new
probably for
you this whole entire Trail we just
found it like four weeks
ago it goes under the
highway oh my God cookout is going to be
on the right
when we come out of the tunnel cookout
is going to be right there oh my
God oh my
God you think it's important for I
agree it feels like this is slower but I
don't care cuz it's
pretty this path is amazing man and it
was here it's been here the entire time
all four years I've been riding and I
did not know I wanted to slap
myself you know I found
it Ride with GPS sha all the other stuff
didn't have it right kamut didn't have
it Ride with GPS had
it I was like hey wait there's a line
that goes underneath the highway what
the
hell oh what was that
noise something's getting low on battery
I don't know what maybe one of my
mics I might go to monal mode on
accident here in a
bit oh
well trying to get the stereo thing
working
little bit of a hill
here look at this this is where we
should have our coffees that's where we
should have the coffee meet up right
there that's a perfect
place you know what else about going
this direction is the light the light
illuminates things instead of getting in
the
camera comes the tunnel on the highway
you can hear it
look at that
thing honestly I've never seen it from
this
side it's behind that wall no wonder we
couldn't see it
before here we
go passeng your seat
bels happy trails
to
you until we meet
again la la la
la I'm not done I should say I should I
should say that for my song at the end
b b Bop one from David
lero that's just a jiggalo I'm mixing
just a jiggalo up with happy
trails they sound the
same I'm just a
jigo and everywhere I go there's a bike
that didn't
survive what's over here is there water
water pleas said There Be
Water there is no oh there's a cute
little girl in her bike learning how to
ride her bike her first time how cool is
that so
cute it's like a bus transfer station
there's a brewery up here keep me away
from the
brewery keep me away from the brewery no
breweries
allowed I'm trying really hard to
go alcohol less for a while just because
of the health Factor not because of any
other reason
and here's
cookout not right tunnel that's the F
tunnel they're Paving
here God I want to bur her so bad now
you got show you the trick
here lay your bike down watch I'll show
you I will show
you do
this lay your bike down like that
and then pick it back
up here is feel somebody keep people
keep telling me
that go
ahead
and I don't like it because that makes
me want it
more Beard's poison did you see the news
recently just came out the Mormons are
right on that
the World Health Organization made an
official announcement despite all the
beer Lobby against them alcohol Lobby
against them that there is no amount of
alcohol you can consume
safely I
know I'm a buzz kill aren't I I'm so
sorry it was such big news the guy from
gcn he's famous for drinking lots of
beer had to make a special video about
how it's going to curb his drinking
habits he still has like two beers a day
or a week or
thing I I got nothing against people who
drink beer or myself drinking beer I
just number one I get
fat there is no single case reason for
me to be fat more than
beer when I regularly drink alcohol I
blimp out faster than any other
thing and I'm not sure
why not just the alcohol even when I'm
working out and
stuff it's because it's really
dense
and I think it might have something to
do with the cortisol I don't
know I don't sleep as
well yet I've been drinking I don't know
I look don't listen to me do what you
want but I
personally I'm trying
to turn my beer and take down I'm also
56 57
and the science is really clear on that
old people don't metabolized beer nearly
as
fast beer is absolutely toxic to your
system the alcohol is so the only
way it
survives is how fast your
body makes that beer into something not
toxic you can study the whole
process of the
conversion if you want there's lots of
videos
that as you age that conversion stops
happening which means that the beer in
its completely toxic destructive
State um stays in your body longer as a
toxin as opposed to being process and
getting in left your body as you age
you're unable to do that that's why when
you wake up you get you feel like you
get hit with a freid train more by
drinking the same amount you drink when
you were a
kid Stephen coar actually made a good
joke about that once he had another talk
show host the young black guy what's his
name from the he filled in for for The
Daily Show and they were talking about
drinking and stuff and St CO's like I
can't do that I wake up and I have a
headache for two days like you know it
completely knocks me out he's like what
no
man it's an old man thing
but this old man wants to stay
healthy and jacked
so unfortunately I know I hate to be the
buzz kill but that means I got to buzz I
got to kill the buzz a little
bit so I'm thinking about getting high
instead I should do a gummy and go on a
bike
ride would I get in trouble with switch
for
that I did not do that today by the way
this just is just normal Rob
High where's pixel is pixel here still
pixel do you do you
ride it's a wor
Shug for desire taxation
yeah well that that's why I'm kind of
okay with like THC and stuff like that
because if you look I like I like having
a fun little mental alteration in my
mental state it's kind of fun why do you
think I like endurance SPS so much still
bike's feeling great do you think I can
maintain control on these Trails you
look I'm not going to hold you
accountable if I screw up again like
when I lost my
teeth alcohol did that squirrel what's
up squirrel oh my
God someone clipped the
squirrels so many squirrels
today wa I must have seen at least 25
squirrels and two
bunnies I kind of don't want to go that
way
I kind of want to go this way
today I don't know why I just do let's
see where it takes us where will the
greenway take
us I think it was another one I think it
was another
squirrel uhhuh I think there were two
squirrels
involved dude people get people grind
squirrels up in there oh there's
the paddle board I mean there's a pickle
ball
okay this is now a part of the trail of
the trail officially also because
there's
water and there's art there's actually
art on the screen what the hell why am I
haven't been on doing this the whole
time please have
water it's going to be turned off
because it's past Labor Day I'll bet
you maybe not Maybe not maybe we're
lucky water
sorry
for gloring in your
ear that's your
bike fire bik though
yeah how much you take yeah I'm going to
try 10 m but and I I don't know if I can
even talk about it if I'm doing it on
stream I think it's a twitch
violation you can get kicked out for
that
[Music]
oh
no
oo I don't think I can do that it's too
steep I wanted to though it was very
tempting maybe next time
casual smoking
H
yeah yeah there's a lot of I can smell
it on the trail a lot
too of course I'm not a smoker I don't
like the smoke I don't like the lung
lungs
thing I do like downtown
Huntersville Oldtown Huntersville that's
what this is a brewery right
here this is kind of fun I got to come
there's a lot of art here
too there's a brewery right here there's
a bike pump
station they have events here all the
time too so we need to make this a
regular that's a dog park I
think yeah we need to make this
officially part of the route this is fun
to watch people
watching MS
somebody dropped there oil there is that
cooking oil look
like Mama Mia I'm a
restaurant by Italian
cuisine named Mama
Mia I doubt
it here's what way waited out the
hurricane can you see me
God I love that Pub I love it and right
by there is the 80s
arcade the 80s arcade we should go in
there over here is where I got the
sardines the bodega where I got the
sardines I met the father of the
father-in-law of the guy from
neot Mike is his name I think
here's where I crashed the Boy Scout
trop free food party
once long time ago you know what if we
go right
here I we go into that that the Oldtown
Huntersville
area
yeah
huh I'm trying to think here what we
could do
here we're extending the route by quite
a lot actually by doing this so that's
why I'm trying to
decide I I want to keep it relatively
fast there's some interesting stuff down
there
but I don't think that's the right thing
I actually feel like we should probably
not turn off the road CU this road is
really
dangerous that main road is pain it's
because they made this big sidewalk here
they expect the bikes to go on the
sidewalk
and of course I don't like that
but also crpe mtle lined with crpe
mtle I think if we're going to do this
we should stay on the main route and
then just do the
left and turn turn off right
there either that or we we take a look
back there and go through the roundout
if you guys know the route if you do
exclamation point route or and map you
can see X map you can see where I am and
where I normally go if you
care we're in Oldtown Huntersville
here here's a
bodega sardines
Bodega I had a burrito from the Mexican
truck it was right here
usually here's what I have great there's
Great Clips of me like a massive
thunderstorm outside
there I should go get
tattoo I should go get a
tattoo they're doing they all got
college football shirts on you see
that oh
L
out I this is where I worked for a day
anybody remember
that I worked out of my Subaru from here
they have another water water fountain
right there they also have those those
um plugs I think are turned off
though I can't
remember I think they are I think those
plug are from this is another one of
those cases where they want the bikers
to be on the
sidewalk which I really don't like but
whatever thany so what's
up all right let's uh
here's why I don't like being on the
sidewalk cuz pedestrians need the
sidewalk not
me there's actually a road right next to
that I usually take on the other side of
the
tracks man there's like a really really
really old
graveyard super old
I love walking around in graveyards and
reading the gravestones and wondering
what the people
did here's all the new
construction by the water tower whatever
that thing's going to be
and here's the
roundabout It's usually the one I take
to get to the
tunnel
Trail we're not going to go on it we're
just taking a right here
hour and 49 minutes yesterday it took me
two hours to get done with the whole
thing it's cuz I'm wandering
this is a road they repaved over the
last year lot of you will remember when
it
was a lot worse and then it was Ro it
was dirt we couldn't do it and then it's
paved
now it's kind of fun to take historical
note of the changes of the to the
infrastructure while you're riding on
them all the
time kind of
fun I got salt in my eye
hey assment have fun
lurking I'm always here
electric scooters
oh black black Farm Road is this going
to be a killer
climb cuz it's if we get it
downhill such perfect weather I mean it
is just so perfect
oh
boy I don't even dare look at
it thanks ugly appreciate it I should
probably mention those of you if you
want to show appreciation in ways that
don't cost money make a
clip make a clip of your favorite thing
really really helps me out like you have
no idea how much it helps out because I
can just publish a clip straight to Tik
Tok and YouTube and
everything and uh it saved me a ton of
work so I appreciate that I really
do I know I've been I've been uploading
a lot of your Clips actually I went
through some of
recently
so I wish it would show you oh I guess
it does
yeah I super appreciate
it you look when you
laugh got to keep ugly laughing
then oh doggy
here we go it should be a big old
downhill and a big old
uphill cuz that's how it
works did every going to stop sign
yes but I check both ways and it was a
right
turn oh God
nice thank
you you think it would post it to the
chat automatically but I guess
not on the lower sections I actually
pull them
up like climbing the SE how about that a
good
chance gear down let me watch the clips
I'm climbing this boring Hill Minecraft
mode really
wait my internet does not like that
probably not do that
oh this
is this is that
one this is the
golf
club one of the golf
clubs this is be
interesting I kind of feel like this is
equally interesting this direction as
the other that's really good
I can do both ways you
know feels ribs filled up pretty good
yeah I don't know if you saw but I've
been doing restorative yoga and not
aranga and that's been really great for
my
ribs L less of a
that's that's hard to recover
from more
easy less
hard yeah I wish I'd gotten that gravel
crash on stream that would have been
amazing tell you what though it
hurts it hurt
I didn't feel the rib thing until I was
walking home I had to walk about two
miles
home and I didn't start feeling the rib
thing I was trying to push the
bike and I could star to feel the rib
thing pretty sure I cracked
it you know I can already tell you
what's going to
yeah so you have a record of it it's
like yo did you see that wipe out dude
yo bro did you see that gnarly wipe out
nobody says do that
anymore except for old gen
xers okay I tell you right now the thing
is going to suck about this I on this
like 9% downhill grade with all this
momentum and my brakes are on
because of this right here cuz I got to
get on this path and not
die oh God hope all my stuff is still
attached
what that wasn't that bad I was thinking
it would be a lot worse than that
am my Sterling still here let me check
it yep he still
there
okay golf
guy sh
going a lot of times that's true right
for a mountain bike
especially ugly I am going to get back
on the mountain bike I got my other
modem so now I have two
modems
and we have mountain bike trails that
are by a cell tower
so I am going to pull out my God I don't
know when probably after I get moved in
November I don't know if I hope they
don't close the trail completely that'll
suck I really hope they don't
cuz in the fall there's really no reason
there is a lot of leaves
but I don't know we'll see but the point
is there's a trail and there's a tower
so yeah Mye Fisher needs a tune up it's
got needs break I need to believe the
brakes and they're
old need changeing up
too I love those days though those
those mountain bike trail days we had
this year in the late spring they were
some of my
favorite favorite time on the bike this
year you're going back and thinking L
what was your favorite time on a bike
right that was got to be one of the
top so much
fun and I went back to writing my to
wear in my camera instead of trying to
mount it to my anars which is just dumb
the other day I was telling people how
smart you are for your rig that has it
on your
chin because your head's like a natural
damper for all the vibration and
stuff this is this is an interesting
dilemma if I go that way I have to deal
with that Hill if I go this way I have
to deal with
traffic so but it's
plat I'm going to try this
way head's the natural Kimble yeah
that's why I put in I remember when I
tried to live stream running 5K and
stuff put in either holding a gimbal
handheld gimbal or
putting putting a camera on your hel on
your
helmet on top of your head headlamp
camera absolutely the best especially if
for running cuz even even in the center
of your chest we tried this with the
GoPro and it you could it was just
annoying it would make you seasick cuz
you're like going back and forth back
and
forth I think I could probably do it
with this rig I have
now because I have a much much
tighter chest
harness you know the no dancing monkeys
one and
then you know I got the gimbal on the
pocket 3 which totally does is just fine
with
running so I think I probably could try
a 5k if I wanted to but I don't know
we'll
see yeah if you don't have that stuff
putting something on your head it's just
so much better
plus your chin is kind of where you you
the point of view of the actual
biker especially for like uro stuff
downhill God I those those videos are so
amazing those guys the stuff they
do absolutely amazing we can even see
that from their perspective
meanwhile there's a clip of me showing
my hand hitting the Blurred out hand
hitting the pavement right before I
knocked my teeth
out that's my number one clip to this
day it's still my number
one I did that just for the
views who needs teeth I needed the views
there's actually people who do that they
manufacture actual physical drama to get
more attention on social
media you guys know Andy Dick the former
comedian I just saw a whole True
Hollywood Story about that dude and how
he's been doing that very thing
think I didn't good with a YouTuber
who is uh famous
for capitalizing on people's people's
drama oh wait that's not my
turn I this is kind of
dangerous not going to
lie looks like we might want to do this
on Sunday and Saturday when the traffic
is
light I got no
shoulder not going to go over any for
it REM I got to post a picture of that
farmers market shop right there you
can't see behind the trees
so
cool po
helmet what's funny is my helmet never
hit the
ground just my face took all the burnt
of it that was literally it my face and
my pinky one of my
fingers that was it my
thing damn where's my
turn this is getting
weird share the
road good Lu with
that too slow as a culprit you know what
it's
funny if I what was C with is why I
didn't
have uh reaction
time if I had had one less beer I could
have I could have I could have easily
dodged that
car I've done it many many times but not
that
day but it
was I don't know if going too SL was a
culprit I don't know I I do the problem
was I tried to
stop
right if if I had hit the
gas and tried to turn I probably would
have went down anyway because of the
turn
angle I you could watch a million
times and yeah I
think I think if I had not hit the
brakes at
all I probably could have sped around it
but all kinds of other negative
possibilities could have happened with
that like I could have gone down under
the wheels I could have come on to the
another head-on you know collision with
another car coming the other
way so my instinct was to slow
down but yeah it's hard it's hard to
know I didn't get my I would if I got my
I'm kind of this is really morbid to say
it
but I can live without front teeth I
cannot live without working
fingers if I had put my feet hands down
with no gloves on
to block that ball I at least would have
broken my collar bone for sure but it
probably would have gnarled my hands and
then I wouldn't have been able to
code and it's like if I can't
code you know at the time I was a
contractor but now I'm like I've got
disability insurance and everything so
that would cover me and I could heal up
and I would be fine thank God I'm I feel
so much better now it's one of the
reasons I don't mind biking so much
because I have disability now so if I if
I were to go down and take my hands out
and couldn't type I couldn't participate
I could still make money I could still
support my family but back then I
couldn't
have oh this reminds me I have gone here
backwards we came on here backwards with
the pelaton once with the
pros yeah it's much more photogenic from
this angle
yeah can actually read it because I'm
going so
slow by Centennial
Farm establish an 1823
car pass to
me there's cow
Hollow usually the cow's hanging out
there not today though
here's the killer Hill I was talking
about oh God
dictate can almost do that you can some
people do
that I went to school with the guy was
legally blind he would stick his eyeball
up to the camera screen did the computer
screen and look at every cursor type he
could see what
the the letter
was and he was a good student he was a
great student
horse see
that's this busy
road that
dang
hopefully I thought that was a snake on
the ground I didn't see what it was at
first and I then I started thinking it
was a snake
for
oh is it smell
good some kind of dinner some kind of
some kind of casserole
line right turn that idea I'm doing it
anyway can't give up this momento
man uh-oh
whoopsie all right this is this is going
to be way more dangerous this particular
part cuz I'm on the wrong side of the
road but again a good good time to
probably only want to flip this when I
do low traffic
what's that
about one of my mics is about to give up
figure out way to do power to the mics
so I never have to think about
that everything else I got covered for
like 15
hours so nice not have to think about
your IRL
Stu I just need an ultra light battery
Bank
it'll just get me another four hours
just double the time of these DJI Mike
twos that I
have I do wish I do worry about
vibration noise though from that being
connected to a
cable notoriously it's bad on these
mics I don't know we'll
see we shall see
another oh this is horrible I'm going to
have all this momentum on this really
really popular
intersection and I'm not going to be
able to
stop that's that's not good okay take
another of that
Rob just looking at the places that
are
problematic this is fun though
tell me I turned RTL
on it's been off this whole time and
nobody said
anything oh my
God okay it's on now I just turned it
on that bums me out big time
yeah the map was there but it wasn't on
it wasn't turned on it wasn't changing
on the screen
oh well my fault I should have
noticed oh my God this hell is a killer
woo
oh
boy it's all climbing to get
home yeah I just barely start it I need
to do a redo I
know I God my Garin was
on I've had to do that before I've
forgot to turn my garment on
and so
I've uploaded the RTL GPS to my straa or
whatever
and yeah looks like I did the right it
does exactly the same
thing super nice to have that option if
you like to track this stuff like I
do all the people on YouTube are like
this guy's stats are totally wrong
another the reason I even put them there
I don't even think people really care or
do they
we had we had what's his name here e ex
EXA
whatever they were saying they like the
stats
so and they'd be they'd be fine with it
having it in meters as
well
so who
knows oh my God that is one Steep Hill
right there what is that
7% grade
2 hours 21 minute ride it's going to be
a three-hour
ride but we did a lot of fun stuff
so every day
4:00 come hell high water I swear to
God this is not all downhill I promise
you maybe it seems that way to you
yeah there's another 6% grade right here
I bet I'm going to it'll tell me in a
second it's when I look like I'm walking
like Zed said looks like you're walking
you are you
walking no it's hard
5% I was wrong okay on there it is
6% it was a 6% grade I called
it I'm getting better calling the
grades wow look at how quiet traffic is
remote
job first month four hour
commute
um I that's a that's a tough
one that's a tough one I I would I would
make sure that they're not just lying to
you to use you for a month and get rid
of your
you make really sure that that's been
known to happen people will even not not
hire you and and give out actual work
projects to people and say you need to
do this project they really they do this
and about it's insane you need to do
this project to prove you can do it and
it's actual work they need done and then
they don't hire the people and they it's
like a thing it's un Unthinkable that
that would happen but it absolutely does
happen
so um
I would say just remember that you are
the one in
control
uh and
stuff hey I'm I'm headed down there
thank
you if you're then yeah I would do it
if you're positive it's 100% remote and
you get it in
writing make sure it's written into your
contract that way so they can't change
it the first
week those are going to be changing job
again which is also a
fine if you got the skills for the job
then a month of training even if it goes
bad is
good just consider it like a a seriously
immense intense you know people pay what
1288 to $2,000 for a month of really
intense training
so
yeah yeah sear knows what we're talking
about how's it going sear by the way you
got your your temporary job now getting
you stabilize so you can buy build up
your lab and everything hey by the way
I'm in the same boat as you and with
well I mean not with inar job but with
regard to the
lab my server died made a video about it
so I have to buy a new
server I I made a two-hour video trying
to decide if I should buy a server or
make my lab in the
cloud
and ended up concluding that I'm going
to buy a server but I got to wait till
November because we we're paying double
rent
still
stuff I want to go turn it on and it
wouldn't boot
I know because of the be the
beeps it does five beeps in a
row which according to HP means the
motherboard is
fried
so I could part it out and make another
one and all that
but I don't get I don't care to do all
that I did all that when I was a kid
just want a computer that works so I can
practice doing what I get paid
for and that is riding kickass backend
apis
and I don't I don't need to know how to
do networking or you know Rec
reconfigure a disc or any of
that drives are completely stable yeah
all the other components are GPU
everything by commun what do you what
are your options on the commute
PJ do you
can you do
um can you do any kind of public
transportation probably not 4our
commute train seriously oh you you
locked
out you know what's so great about that
you can
dude I don't know if you're a dude I'm
just saying
dude
um that's
perfect consider this month like you're
really really intense intense intense
focus training and spent every waking
second on that
train it's wonderful the train is
awesome that's what I am I'm not saying
anything bad about the train it's
actually really
good
um the train you can Dude to this day I
look at buses and I get all warm and
fuzzy inside because I did so much
learning I gave myself a master's in
computer science on the on the bus on
the
train
and I mean if you had to drive that
would
no but if you can do it on the
train is it if it's a 4our commute both
ways or two hours one way 2 hours back
what is it is it an eight total hours of
commuting if it's eight hours commuting
think of it
as think of it as a
solid day 8 hour day of self-directed
learning and make your God this is
exciting so you can make yourself a plan
right you can make yourself a training
plan I'm going to go through this book
then I'm going to go through this book
you can bring your laptop even on sun
trains and you can use that
time to really kick
butt and you can just put your
headphones in or put your earplugs in
and ignore your neighbors if you put
headphones in it won't talk to you and
you have all that you have that have all
that time in the car you wasting it
because the best you can do is a podcast
or
something but in a in a
train you can really dig into that stuff
and you can get super focused I used to
get so focused that I would miss my
stop sometimes I fall asleep and miss my
stop I think I'm excited for you now if
it's just a
month and by the way if it's just a
month and it turns out to not be your
thing you can now say you have a month
of 4-Hour commutes every day doing
directed learning and if you prepare a
learning program for yourself you can
put that on your resume think about
that if you prepare a directed learning
plan for yourself that you document and
you have a journal you have a log of it
and you follow that while you're on the
on the train whether or not you like the
job you're going for you'll have that
you'll have that kickass bullet
point and people will actually hire you
just for that bullet point if you do
that they will
because they're going to show that you
an independent learner that's what they
want to
hire I'm s kind of exciting for
you yeah yall need to hook up in Discord
or something help each other out
where was
back
yeah
again you
put make it so that you
have like I don't know I know que up a
whole bunch of skill
stack
videos on your way back back you know
while you're
walking I I would say that's a totally
that's a definite
yes if it's at all remotely related to
what you want to do and there's a chance
you can do it remotely which is really
hard to find today really hard I mean
anybody will tell you on this chat how
hard a buly remote job starting salary
job starting job is super hard to find
if it truly is
that I would say that
possibility is worth the risk especially
since the time that you consider
possibly being wasted or lost it could
be totally invested into a documented
learning plan that can then go into your
resume and further your job potential
for the next
job so I would I would be a yes for sure
on that one
I don't know what's worse the sidewalk
or the speed bump on that one
would be the first time someone's found
a job by someone they met on my stream
including
me that's how I found my
job if you're watching us on
YouTube and you happen to see this come
join
us we each other survive the tech
world and 7%
grades feels so
good right now
we're going to finish in downtown
Davidson and as a rule I think we're
going to start
at at um spirited
Cyclery but I don't plan on ending there
I think I'll
probably always end in Davidson where we
can grab a beer or a coffee or some
food with a
group those of you don't know who just
went to the end of the video
um and I probably will probably try to
find somebody to raid
here about to the
end
um I'm going to be starting to do I'm
going to propose at least hopefully I
can post to the bulletin board at this
at The
Cyclery uh a group ride at least once a
month maybe twice a
month if you're in the Davidson area if
you're in this area and you want join me
for any part of it I'd love to have
you officially or
unofficially so if you came across this
video yeah I ran it the car right next
to me
stopped hopefully they won't get too mad
I smell barbecue
this climb isn't nearly as bad as I
envisioned it
why
not I like this direction I have to do
this more
coming into the town of
Davidson Ivy leag college town
some nights there might actually be a
football game going on I'm not into it
but might see the
crowd actually I think they don't play
in that Stadium anymore I think they
built a new stadium last year I think
they play that's on the other side of
Campus
who should we looking raid
here who's
on last Smiles is watching movies
everybody's a
twitchcon looks like Anita got a face
job sweet Anita
[Music]
there's nobody in the IRL
category all right we are going to leave
you
here and the Beautiful town of Davidson
[Music]
that from twitchcon Tio Tony made to him
yesterday zier portable
bless all day New York let's raid
him raid all day New York
seconds till the raid what do we want to
talk about
anything f v lots of internal promotions
that's a great
idea hey great that's usually the way it
is when you're first getting
in as it Nike they paid 30 grand a year
can you believe that I was their Web
Master I was their Web Master I was in
charge of their entire intern internal
Web Master web website and all the
hosting and helping every every single
Department hosted I'm kind of bragging
but they want pay 30 grand this was
1997 but still in today dollars that
would be like what 60k
maybe when I when IBM picked me up IBM
IBM offered
me
75,000 and I said fine I'm there I'm
done it doubled my salary
this was in the
990s and I've since I mean I probably
shouldn't say but I've more than doubled
that since
then uh five are you going in and got it
got 550k
pot yeah you had five when was that
pixel what year was that before
inflation oh good God where's the raid
oh 3 seconds
bye bye bye bye
all right every